********************  WARNING  *****************************
Do not run this driver’s installer (Setup.exe) from a USB
storage device (ie. external USB hard drive or USB thumb 
drive). For proper installation, please copy driver files 
to a local hard drive folder and run from there.
************************************************************
*
*  Production Version Release
* 
*  Microsoft Windows* 7 
*
*  Intel(R) USB 3.0 eXtensible Host Controller:  3.0.5.69				
*
*  April 2015
*
*  NOTE:  This document refers to systems containing the 
*         following Intel processors/chipsets: 
*
*	Intel(R) 8 Series/C220 series Chipset Family
*	4th generation Intel(R) Core(TM) Processors
*	Intel(R) C610 series Chipset Family      
*	Intel(R) 9 Series Chipset Family
*	Intel(R) Pentium(R) Processor or Intel(R)	            
*	Celeron(R) Processor N- & J- Series
*	5th generation Intel(R) Core(TM) Processors
*	Intel(R) Core(TM) M Processor
*	
*  Installation Information
*
*  This document makes references to products developed by
*  Intel. There are some restrictions on how these products
*  may be used, and what information may be disclosed to
*  others. Please read the Disclaimer section and contact
*  your Intel field representative if you would like more
*  information.
*
************************************************************
************************************************************
*  DISCLAIMER: Intel is making no claims of usability,
*  efficacy or warranty.  The INTEL SOFTWARE LICENSE
*  AGREEMENT contained herein completely defines the license
*  and use of this software.
*
*  This document contains information on products in the 
*  design phase of development. The information here is 
*  subject to change without notice. Do not finalize a 
*  design with this information.
************************************************************
************************************************************

************************************************************
*  CONTENTS OF THIS DOCUMENT
************************************************************

This document contains the following sections:

1.  System Requirements
2.  Localized Language Abbreviations
3.  Installing the Software
4.  Verifying Installation of the Software
5.  Identifying the Software Version Number
6.  Installation switches available
7.  Uninstalling the software

************************************************************
*  1.  SYSTEM REQUIREMENTS
************************************************************

1. The system must contain one of the following Intel
   Processors/Chipsets:
                    
	Intel(R) 8 Series Chipset Family.
	4th Generation Intel(R) Core(TM) Processors.
	Intel(R) C610 series Chipset Family.
	Intel(R) 9 Series Chipset Family.
	Intel(R) Pentium(R) Processor or Intel(R)
	Celeron(R) Processor N- & J- Series.
	5th generation Intel(R) Core(TM) Processors
	Intel(R) Core(TM) M Processor.

2. The software should be installed on systems with at
   least 1 GB of system memory.

3. There should be sufficient hard disk space in the <TEMP>
   directory on the system in order to install this
   software.

   The drivers included with this distribution package are
   designed to function with all released versions of
   Microsoft Windows* 7 OS available at the time of release 
   of this package.

Please check with your system provider to determine the
operating system and Intel Chipset used in your system.
************************************************************
*  2.  LOCALIZED LANGUAGE ABBREVIATIONS
************************************************************

The following list contains the hexadecimal key of all
languages into which the driver has been localized. You may
have to refer to this section while using this document.
    Code #, Language, Language Code
	0401 -> Arabic (International), ARA
	0804 -> Chinese (Simplified), CHS
	0404 -> Chinese (Traditional), CHT, 
	0405 -> Czech, CSY
	0406 -> Danish, DAN
	0407 -> German, DEU
	0408 -> Greek, ELL
	0409 -> English (United States), ENU
	040A -> Spanish, ESP
	040B -> Finnish, FIN
	040C -> French (International), FRA
	040D -> Hebrew, HEB
	040E -> Hungarian, HUN
	0410 -> Italian, ITA
	0411 -> Japanese, JPN
	0412 -> Korean, KOR
	0413 -> Dutch, NLD
	0414 -> Norwegian, NOR
	0415 -> Polish, PLK
	0416 -> Portuguese (Brazil), PTB
	0816 ->Portuguese (Portugal), PTG
	0419 -> Russian, RUS
	041B -> Slovak, SKY
	0424 -> Slovenian, SLV
	041D -> Swedish, SVE
	041E -> Thai, THA
	041F -> Turkish, TRK


************************************************************
*  3.  INSTALLING THE SOFTWARE
************************************************************

General Installation Notes:

1. The operating system must be installed prior to the 
   installation of the driver.

2. This installation procedure is specific only to the 
   version of driver and installation file included in this 
   release.

3. This procedure assumes that all of the software 
   associated with this release is located in the same 
   directory.

INSTALLATION INSTRUCTIONS 
------------------------------------------------------------

To install from a Web download, you will download either a
ZIP file or an EXE file from the Web.

a. If it is an EXE file, double-click the file you 
   downloaded and specify a location into which the  driver
   files will be extracted. Click "Unzip" and the files 
   will extract. Click "OK" on the next window, then click 
   "Close". 

b. If it is a ZIP file, double-click the file you downloaded
   and choose “Extract all files”. Next,  browse to a 
   destination folder in which the files can be placed and 
   choose “Extract”.

************************************************************
*   Operating Systems supported
************************************************************

Intel(R) 8 Series Chipset Family
4th Generation Intel(R) Core(TM) Processors
Intel(R) C610 series Chipset Family
Intel(R) 9 Series Chipset Family
Intel(R) Pentium(R) Processor or Intel(R)
Celeron(R) Processor N- & J- Series
5th generation Intel(R) Core(TM) Processors
Intel(R) Core(TM) M Processor:
•  Windows* 7 Operating System (both 32-bit and 64-bit 
   versions).

Intel(R) C220 series chipset family
Intel(R) C610 series Chipset Family:
•  Windows* 7 Operating System (both 32-bit and 64-bit 
   versions).
•  Windows* Server 2008 R2 Operating System.
•  Windows* Small Business Server 2008 Operating System.


************************************************************
*   Microsoft Windows* 7 and Windows* Server 2008 
    "Setup.exe" Installation
************************************************************

1. Locate the hard drive directory where the driver files 
   are stored with the browser or the explore feature of 
   Windows*.

2. Double click the “Setup.exe” from this directory.

3. The Install dialog will appear.
 
4. Click “Next” to continue.

5. Read License Agreement and click “Yes” to proceed.

6. Review Readme File Information and click “Next” to 
   proceed.

7. When the “Setup Progress” is complete click “Next” 
   to proceed.

8. Lastly, the “Setup Complete” screen appears so click
   “Finish” to restart your computer.
   
************************************************************
*  4.  VERIFYING INSTALLATION OF THE SOFTWARE
************************************************************
1. Click "Start" then right click on "Computer" button and 
   then click on properties.

2. Click on the "Device Manager" selection on the left.

3. Select "Universal Serial Bus controllers". The Intel(R) 
   USB 3.0 eXtensible Host Controller device and Intel(R) 
   USB 3.0 Root Hub device should be listed and not yellow 
   banged. 
   If not, the driver is not installed correctly. 

************************************************************
*  5. IDENTIFYING THE SOFTWARE VERSION NUMBER
************************************************************

1. Click "Start" then right click on "Computer" button and 
   then click on properties.

2. Click on the "Device Manager" selection on the left.

3. Select "Universal Serial Bus controllers" then double 
   click on the Intel(R) USB 3.0 eXtensible Host Controller 
   device or Intel(R) USB 3.0 Root Hub device.

4. Click on "Driver" tab and note the driver version.

************************************************************
*  6. INSTALLATION SWITCHES AVAILABLE
************************************************************
The switches in the SETUP.EXE file will have the following 
syntax. 
Switches are not case sensitive and may be specified in any 
order (except for the -s switch). Switches must be separated 
by spaces.
SETUP [-?]

-? Displays help dialog.

************************************************************
*  7. UNINSTALLING THE SOFTWARE
************************************************************
NOTE: This procedure assumes the above installation process
was successful. This uninstallation procedure is specific
only to the version of the driver and installation files
included in this package.

1. Click on the "Start" button, then click on the "Control 
   Panel" icon, and then double click on "Programs and 
   Features", right click on "Intel(R) USB 3.0 eXtensible 
   Host Controller Driver" and select "Uninstall" option

2. Click "Next" to uninstall the driver.

3. Click on "Finish" button to restart the computer.


***************************************************************************
* INTEL SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT 
* (OEM / IHV / ISV Distribution & Single User)
***************************************************************************

IMPORTANT - READ BEFORE COPYING, INSTALLING OR USING. 
Do not use or load this software and any associated materials (collectively, 
the “Software”) until you have carefully read the following terms and 
conditions. By loading or using the Software, you agree to the terms of this 
Agreement. If you do not wish to so agree, do not install or use the Software.

Please Also Note:
	If you are an Original Equipment Manufacturer (OEM), Independent 
	Hardware Vendor (IHV), or Independent Software Vendor (ISV), this 
	complete LICENSE AGREEMENT applies;
	If you are an End-User, then only Exhibit A, the INTEL SOFTWARE 
	LICENSE AGREEMENT, applies.

For OEMs, IHVs, and ISVs:

LICENSE. This Software is licensed for use only in conjunction with Intel 
component products.  Use of the Software in conjunction with non-Intel 
component products is not licensed hereunder. Subject to the terms of this 
Agreement, Intel grants to You a nonexclusive, nontransferable, worldwide, 
fully paid-up license under Intel’s copyrights to:
	a) use, modify and copy Software internally for Your own development 
	   and maintenance purposes; and
	b) modify, copy and distribute Software, including derivative works 
	   of the Software, to Your end-users, but only under a license 
	   agreement with terms at least as restrictive as those contained 
	   in Intel's Final, Single User License Agreement, attached as 
	   Exhibit A; and
	c) modify, copy and distribute the end-user documentation which may 
	   accompany the Software, but only in association with the Software.


If You are not the final manufacturer or vendor of a computer system or 
software program incorporating the Software, then You may transfer a copy of 
the Software, including derivative works of the Software (and related end-user 
documentation) to Your recipient for use in accordance with the terms of this 
Agreement, provided such recipient agrees to be fully bound by the terms hereof.  
You shall not otherwise assign, sublicense, lease, or in any other way transfer 
or disclose Software to any third party. You shall not reverse- compile, 
disassemble or otherwise reverse-engineer the Software.

Except as expressly stated in this Agreement, no license or right is granted 
to You directly or by implication, inducement, estoppel or otherwise. Intel 
shall have the right to inspect or have an independent auditor inspect Your 
relevant records to verify Your compliance with the terms and conditions of 
this Agreement.

CONFIDENTIALITY.   If You wish to have a third party consultant or 
subcontractor ("Contractor") perform work on Your behalf which involves access 
to or use of Software, You shall obtain a written confidentiality agreement 
from the Contractor which contains terms and obligations with respect to access 
to or use of Software no less restrictive than those set forth in this Agreement 
and excluding any distribution rights, and use for any other purpose. Otherwise, 
You shall not disclose the terms or existence of this Agreement or use Intel's 
name in any publications, advertisements, or other announcements without Intel's 
prior written consent.  You do not have any rights to use any Intel trademarks 
or logos.

OWNERSHIP OF SOFTWARE AND COPYRIGHTS. Title to all copies of the Software 
remains with Intel or its suppliers. The Software is copyrighted and protected 
by the laws of the United States and other countries, and international treaty 
provisions. You may not remove any copyright notices from the Software. Intel 
may make changes to the Software, or to items referenced therein, at any time 
and without notice, but is not obligated to support or update the Software. 
Except as otherwise expressly provided, Intel grants no express or implied 
right under Intel patents, copyrights, trademarks, or other intellectual 
property rights. You may transfer the Software only if the recipient agrees to 
be fully bound by these terms and if you retain no copies of the Software.

LIMITED MEDIA WARRANTY.  If the Software has been delivered by Intel on physical 
media, Intel warrants the media to be free from material physical defects for a 
period of ninety (90) days after delivery by Intel. If such a defect is found, 
return the media to Intel for replacement or alternate delivery of the Software 
as Intel may select.

EXCLUSION OF OTHER WARRANTIES. EXCEPT AS PROVIDED ABOVE, THE SOFTWARE IS 
PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, INCLUDING 
WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, NONINFRINGEMENT, OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR 
PURPOSE.  Intel does not warrant or assume responsibility for the accuracy or 
completeness of any information, text, graphics, links or other items contained 
within the Software.

LIMITATION OF LIABILITY. IN NO EVENT SHALL INTEL OR ITS SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE 
FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, LOST PROFITS, 
BUSINESS INTERRUPTION OR LOST INFORMATION) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF OR 
IN-ABILITY TO USE THE SOFTWARE, EVEN IF INTEL HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE 
POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. SOME JURISDICTIONS PROHIBIT EXCLUSION OR 
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR CONSEQUENTIAL OR 
INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. YOU MAY 
ALSO HAVE OTHER LEGAL RIGHTS THAT VARY FROM JURISDICTION TO JURISDICTION. 

TERMINATION OF THIS AGREEMENT. Intel may terminate this Agreement at any 
time if you violate its terms. Upon termination, you will immediately destroy 
the Software or return all copies of the Software to Intel.
 
APPLICABLE LAWS. Claims arising under this Agreement shall be governed by the 
laws of California, excluding its principles of conflict of laws and the 
United Nations Convention on Contracts for the Sale of Goods. You may not 
export the Software in violation of applicable export laws and regulations. 
Intel is not obligated under any other agreements unless they are in writing 
and signed by an authorized representative of Intel.

GOVERNMENT RESTRICTED RIGHTS. The Software is provided with "RESTRICTED RIGHTS." 
Use, duplication, or disclosure by the Government is subject to restrictions as 
set forth in FAR52.227-14 and DFAR252.227-7013 et seq. or their successors. Use 
of the Software by the Government constitutes acknowledgment of Intel's 
proprietary rights therein. Contractor or Manufacturer is Intel Corporation, 
2200 Mission College Blvd., Santa Clara, CA 95052.

 
EXHIBIT “A” 
INTEL SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT (Final, Single User)

IMPORTANT - READ BEFORE COPYING, INSTALLING OR USING. 
Do not use or load this software and any associated materials (collectively, the 
“Software”) until you have carefully read the following terms and conditions. By 
loading or using the Software, you agree to the terms of this Agreement. If you 
do not wish to so agree, do not install or use the Software.

LICENSE. You may copy the Software onto a single computer for your personal, 
noncommercial use, and you may make one back-up copy of the Software, subject to 
these conditions: 
1.	This Software is licensed for use only in conjunction with Intel 
	component products.  Use of the Software in conjunction with non-Intel 
	component products is not licensed hereunder. 
2.	You may not copy, modify, rent, sell, distribute or transfer any part of 
	the Software except as provided in this Agreement, and you agree to 
	prevent unauthorized copying of the Software.
3.	You may not reverse engineer, decompile, or disassemble the Software. 
4.	You may not sublicense or permit simultaneous use of the Software by 
	more than one user.
5.	The Software may contain the software or other property of third party 
	suppliers, some of which may be identified in, and licensed in accordance 
	with, any enclosed “license.txt” file or other text or file. 

OWNERSHIP OF SOFTWARE AND COPYRIGHTS. Title to all copies of the Software remains 
with Intel or its suppliers. The Software is copyrighted and protected by the laws 
of the United States and other countries, and international treaty provisions. You 
may not remove any copyright notices from the Software. Intel may make changes to 
the Software, or to items referenced therein, at any time without notice, but is 
not obligated to support or update the Software. Except as otherwise expressly 
provided, Intel grants no express or implied right under Intel patents, copyrights, 
trademarks, or other intellectual property rights. You may transfer the Software 
only if the recipient agrees to be fully bound by these terms and if you retain 
no copies of the Software.

LIMITED MEDIA WARRANTY.  If the Software has been delivered by Intel on physical 
media, Intel warrants the media to be free from material physical defects for a 
period of ninety (90) days after delivery by Intel. If such a defect is found, 
return the media to Intel for replacement or alternate delivery of the Software 
as Intel may select.

EXCLUSION OF OTHER WARRANTIES. EXCEPT AS PROVIDED ABOVE, THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED 
"AS IS" WITHOUT ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTY OF ANY KIND INCLUDING WARRANTIES 
OF MERCHANTABILITY, NONINFRINGEMENT, OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  Intel 
does not warrant or assume responsibility for the accuracy or completeness of 
any information, text, graphics, links or other items contained within the Software.

LIMITATION OF LIABILITY. IN NO EVENT SHALL INTEL OR ITS SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR 
ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, LOST PROFITS, BUSINESS 
INTERRUPTION, OR LOST INFORMATION) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF OR IN-ABILITY TO 
USE THE SOFTWARE, EVEN IF INTEL HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH 
DAMAGES. SOME JURISDICTIONS PROHIBIT EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR 
IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE 
LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. YOU MAY ALSO HAVE OTHER LEGAL RIGHTS THAT VARY 
FROM JURISDICTION TO JURISDICTION. 

TERMINATION OF THIS AGREEMENT. Intel may terminate this Agreement at any time 
if you violate its terms. Upon termination, you will immediately destroy the 
Software or return all copies of the Software to Intel.
 
APPLICABLE LAWS. Claims arising under this Agreement shall be governed by the 
laws of California, excluding its principles of conflict of laws and the 
United Nations Convention on Contracts for the Sale of Goods. You may not 
export the Software in violation of applicable export laws and regulations. 
Intel is not obligated under any other agreements unless they are in writing 
and signed by an authorized representative of Intel.

GOVERNMENT RESTRICTED RIGHTS. The Software is provided with "RESTRICTED 
RIGHTS." Use, duplication, or disclosure by the Government is subject to 
restrictions as set forth in FAR52.227-14 and DFAR252.227-7013 et seq. or 
their successors. Use of the Software by the Government constitutes 
acknowledgment of Intel's proprietary rights therein. Contractor or 
Manufacturer is Intel Corporation, 2200 Mission College Blvd., Santa Clara, 
CA 95052.

 
SLA/OEM/IHV/RBK/ April 23, 2004
***********************************************************
* DISCLAIMER
***********************************************************
Intel is making no claims of usability, efficacy or 
warranty.The INTEL SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT contained 
herein completely defines the license and use of this 
software.
***********************************************************
Information in this document is provided in connection with
Intel products. Except as expressly stated in the INTEL
SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT contained herein, no license,
express or implied, by estoppel or otherwise, to any
intellectual property rights is granted by this document.
Except as provided in Intel's Terms and Conditions of Sale
for such products, Intel assumes no liability whatsoever,
and Intel disclaims any express or implied warranty,
relating to sale and/or use of Intel products, including
liability or warranties relating to fitness for a 
particular purpose, merchantability or infringement of any
patent, copyright or other intellectual property right. 
Intel products are not intended for use in medical, 
lifesaving, or life-sustaining applications.

***********************************************************
* Intel Corporation disclaims all warranties and 
* liabilities for the use of this document, the software 
* and the information contained herein, and assumes no
* responsibility for any errors which may appear in this
* document or the software, nor does Intel make a 
* commitment to update the information or software 
* contained herein. Intel reserves the right to make 
* changes to this document or software at any time, without
* notice.
***********************************************************

* Other names and brands may be claimed as the property of 
others.

Copyright (c) 2014 Intel Corporation.  All rights reserved.
by Intel on physical media, Intel warrants the media to be
free from material physical defects for a period of ninety 
(90) days after delivery by Intel. If such a defect is 
found, return the media to Intel for replacement or 
alternate delivery of the Software, as Intel may select.

EXCLUSION OF OTHER WARRANTIES. EXCEPT AS PROVIDED ABOVE, 
THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT ANY EXPRESS OR 
IMPLIED WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF
MERCHANTABILITY, NONINFRINGEMENT OR FITNESS FOR A 
PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  Intel does not warrant or assume 
responsibility for the accuracy or completeness of any 
information, text, graphics, links or other items 
contained within the Software.

LIMITATION OF LIABILITY. IN NO EVENT SHALL INTEL OR ITS 
SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING,
WITHOUT LIMITATION, LOST PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION 
OR LOST INFORMATION) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF OR THE 
INABILITY TO USE THE SOFTWARE, EVEN IF INTEL HAS BEEN 
ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. SOME 
JURISDICTIONS PROHIBIT EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
FOR IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL 
DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. 
YOU MAY ALSO HAVE OTHER LEGAL RIGHTS THAT VARY FROM 
JURISDICTION TO JURISDICTION. 

TERMINATION OF THIS AGREEMENT. Intel may terminate this 
Agreement at any time if you violate its terms. Upon 
termination, you will immediately destroy the Software or 
return all copies of the Software to Intel.
 
APPLICABLE LAWS. Claims arising under this Agreement shall 
be governed by the laws of California, excluding its 
principles of conflict of laws and the United Nations 
Convention on Contracts for the Sale of Goods. You may not 
export the Software in violation of applicable export laws 
and regulations. Intel is not obligated under any other 
agreements, unless they are in writing and signed by an 
authorized representative of Intel.

GOVERNMENT RESTRICTED RIGHTS. The Software is provided with
"RESTRICTED RIGHTS." Use, duplication or disclosure by the 
Government is subject to restrictions as set forth in 
FAR52.227-14 and DFAR252.227-7013 et seq. or their 
successors. Use of the Software by the Government 
constitutes acknowledgment of Intel's proprietary rights 
therein. Contractor or Manufacturer is Intel Corporation,
2200 Mission College Blvd., Santa Clara, CA 95052.

 
SLA-ALPHABETA-ORG./RBK/May 20, 2004
***********************************************************
***********************************************************
Information in this document is provided in connection with
Intel products. Except as expressly stated in the INTEL
SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT contained herein, no license,
express or implied, by estoppel or otherwise, to any
intellectual property rights is granted by this document.
Except as provided in Intel's Terms and Conditions of Sale
for such products, Intel assumes no liability whatsoever,
and Intel disclaims any express or implied warranty,
relating to sale and/or use of Intel products, including
liability or warranties relating to fitness for a 
particular purpose, merchantability or infringement of any
patent, copyright or other intellectual property right. 
Intel products are not intended for use in medical, 
lifesaving, or life-sustaining applications.

***********************************************************
* Intel Corporation disclaims all warranties and 
* liabilities for the use of this document, the software 
* and the information contained herein, and assumes no
* responsibility for any errors which may appear in this
* document or the software, nor does Intel make a 
* commitment to update the information or software 
* contained herein. Intel reserves the right to make 
* changes to this document or software at any time, without
* notice.
***********************************************************

* Other names and brands may be claimed as the property of
others.

Copyright (c) Intel Corporation, 2015
